Guide to the Chiron Review Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- March 2006 Acquisition, 1985-2006, undated; 16.33; (26 boxes) + 1 record album storage
  - Poetry events and music performances
    - "The Skinning"
      - the skinning Pit X (unidentified on screen) This has been heavily revised since recorded here X, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0120; 1 (Box 101)
    - "We Are New Since Then, Southern Acc."
      - we are new since then southern acc. 9/10/05 2 min. 13 sec., 2006-ycal-0327-o-0121; 1 (Box 101)
    - Unidentified, 1 33 1/3 vinyl sound disk (Box 102 (Record album storage))
    - "Drakulya: The Vampire Play, by Earl Lee", 25-27 October; YCALMSS836_0021; 1; 01:19:40 (Box 103, Item barcode 39002102317345)
    - "Hatteberg's People: Michael Hathaway, KAKE-TV", 2003 February 16; YCALMSS836_0022; 1; This tape has not been digitized. The contents of the tape are not related to the title in any way. Episodes of "NYPD Blue", "Dragnet", and "Seinfeld" are included. (Box 103, Item barcode 39002102317352)
    - "Poetry Rendezvous, Great Bend", 2004; YCALMSS836_0023; 1; 02:57:21 (Box 103, Item barcode 39002102317360)
    - Moffeit, Tony. "Scheduled Reading", YCALMSS836_0018; 1; 01:03:07 (Box 100, Item barcode 39002102317311)
    - Moffeit, Tony. "Open Mic: Dream of Crazy Horse; Drifter of Dark Dream", ycalmss836_0019; 1; 00:59:46 (Box 100, Item barcode 39002102317329)
    - Moffeit, Tony. "How to Write Blues Poem", YCALMSS836_0020; 1; 00:58:46 (Box 100, Item barcode 39002102317337)
  - Other Papers
    - Address book (Box 89)
    - Address book (Box 96 (Oversize))
    - Scrapbook about the history of Chiron Review (Box 96 (Oversize))
    - Scrapbook about the Chiron Review Poetry Festival (Box 89)
    - Scrapbook about Poetry Rendezvous, 2004 (Box 89)
    - Scrapbook of photographs (Box 97 (Oversize))
    - Scrapbook of photographs, poems, correspondence, and clippings (Box 97 (Oversize))
    - Scrapbook of clippings (Box 98 (Oversize))
    - Art (paintings on paper), 3 (Box 99 (Oversize))
    - Unidentified, 9 3.5 inch computer disks
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0327-o-0008; 1 (Box 104)
      - CHuRch 10.04, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0009; 1 (Box 104)
      - CHURCH 10.4, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0010; 1 (Box 104)
      - Epistle 11/3/02, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0033; 1 (Box 104)
      - Cover Illustration, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0037; 1 (Box 104)
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0327-o-0042; 1 (Box 104)
      - Disk for Betsy Johnson-Miller poems, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0054; 1 (Box 104)
      - From BASINSKI 2 ch, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0066; 1 (Box 104)
      - MOSS LANDING, CALIFORNIA, 2006-ycal-0327-o-0069; 1 (Box 104)
    - Unidentified, 1 CD
- April 2011 Acquisition, 1982-2011, undated; 15.09; (20 boxes)
  Box 121 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Correspondence
    - Balmer Fund, 2009-2010 (Box 106)
    - Duval, Margaret L., Rev., 2 (Box 106)
    - Felder, Brian C. (Box 106)
    - Foos-Graber, Anya, 3 (Box 106)
    - Great Bend Public Library (Great Bend, Kansas) (Box 106)
    - Great Bend Tribune (Box 106)
    - Unsorted (Box 106)
    - Mack, Terry (Box 106)
    - Tate, Russ (Box 106)
    - Unsorted, 21 (Box 106)
    - Unsorted, 34 (Box 107)
    - Unsorted, 8 (Box 108)
  - Chiron Review Issues
    - Kindred Spirit 1-8 (1982-1986) (printed copies), 8 (Box 108)
    - Kindred Spirit 9 (1986 fall) - 17 (1989 winter) (printed copies), 9 (Box 108)
    - Chrion Review 18 (1989 spring) - 44-45 (1995 autumn) (printed copies), 27 (Box 108)
    - Chiron Review 46-47 (1996 spring-1996 summer) - 81 (2005 winter) (printed copies), 36 (Box 109)
    - Chiron Review 82 (2008 Spring) - 84 (2008 autumn) (printed copies), 26 (Box 110)
    - Chiron Review 82 (2008 spring), 2 3.5 inch computer disks
      - CR82, 2011-ycal-44252-0057; 1 (Box 125)
      - CR82, 2011-ycal-44252-0065; 1 (Box 125)
    - Chiron Review 83 (2008 summer) (mechanicals) (Box 118 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 85 (2008 winter) - 87 (2009 summer), 26 (Box 111)
    - Chiron Review 85 (2008 winter), 1 3.5 inch computer disks
      - CR #85 winter 08, 2011-ycal-44252-0044; 1 (Box 125)
    - Chiron Review 87 (2009 summer) - 90 (2010 spring), 34 (Box 112)
    - Chiron Review 88 (2009 autumn) ("CR Photos"), 2009 August 8; 2 DVDs
      - [no label information], 2011-ycal-44252-0016; 1 (Box 123)
      - [no label information], 2011-ycal-44252-0032; 1 (Box 123)
    - Chiron Review 89 (2009 winter) (mechanicals) (Box 118 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review 89 (2009 winter) ("Punk + CR Walmart back-up"), 2009 October; 1 DVD
      - punk + Walmart back-up Oct 2009 CR# 88, 2011-ycal-44252-0029; 1 (Box 123)
      - Chiron Review all-punk issue #88 Dec. 2009, 2011-ycal-44252-0028; 1 (Box 123)
    - Chiron Review 90 (2010 spring) - 93 (2010 winter), 36 (Box 113)
    - Chiron Review 93 (2010 winter) - 94 (2011 spring), 14 (Box 114)
    - Chiron Review Unidentified, 2009; 5 (Box 114)
    - Chiron Review Unidentified, 7 3.5 inch computer disks
      - CR Index working master copy, 2011-ycal-44252-0089; 1 (Box 125)
      - CR Index 12/24/06, 2011-ycal-44252-0091; 1 (Box 125)
      - Kindred Spirit/Chiron Review Index, 2011-ycal-44252-0092; 1 (Box 125)
      - KS/CR Index copy 2 12/16/99, 2011-ycal-44252-0093; 1 (Box 125)
      - CR86, 2011-ycal-44252-0077; 1 (Box 125)
      - CR 84 News 85 Winans inti #85, 2011-ycal-44252-0066; 1 (Box 125)
      - Chiron Review Index RT7 02/13/07, 2011-ycal-44252-0090; 1 (Box 125)
    - Chiron Review Unidentified ("CR Archive 2009"), 1 DVD
      - [no label information], 2011-ycal-44252-0022; 1 (Box 123)
    - Chiron Review Unidentified ("2009-2010"), 1 DVD
      - Chiron Review 2009-2010, 2011-ycal-44252-0020; 1 (Box 123)
    - Chiron Review Unidentified (correspondence), 11 3.5 inch computer disks
      - Chiron Review emails 04/03/07-05/25/07, 2011-ycal-44252-0046; 1 (Box 125)
      - Email 9/19/08-Dec. 31, 2008 Chiron Review, 2011-ycal-44252-0080; 1 (Box 125)
      - Chiron email 11/13/06-04/02/07, 2011-ycal-44252-0048; 1 (Box 125)
      - Chiron Review Letters March 13, 2005-, 2011-ycal-44252-0078; 1 (Box 125)
      - Chiron Review email 01/25/08-4/1/08, 2011-ycal-44252-0079; 1 (Box 125)
      - email 01/30/09-03/14/09 CR, 2011-ycal-44252-0084; 1 (Box 125)
      - Chiron Review email March 16, 2009-, 2011-ycal-44252-0085; 1 (Box 125)
      - email 4/10/08-6/12/08, 2011-ycal-44252-0086; 1 (Box 125)
      - Chiron Review email nov. 4, 2007-01/24/08, 2011-ycal-44252-0083; 1 (Box 125)
      - Chiron Review email July 5, 2007 - 11/03-2007, 2011-ycal-44252-0082; 1 (Box 125)
      - email 6/20/08-9/19/08, 2011-ycal-44252-0081; 1 (Box 125)
    - Chiron Review Unidentifed (mechanicals) (Box 119 (Oversize))
    - Chiron Review Unidentifed (mechanicals), 3 (Box 120 (Oversize))
  - Writings by Michael Hathaway
    - Stumbling into Light, 2 (Box 114)
    - Essays, 2 (Box 114)
    - Poems, 12 (Box 114)
  - Other Writings
    - Alfier, Jeffrey C. "Before the Troubadour Exits" (Box 115)
    - Anderson, Laurie. "Homeland", 1 CD
      - Laurie Anderson "Homeland" 2010, 2011-ycal-44252-0018; 1 (Box 123)
    - Brown, Juanita. "I Shall Sing a Song of Love" (Box 115)
    - Buege, Bill. "Imitations" (Box 115)
    - Buege, Bill. "Jill" (Box 115)
    - Daniel, Hal J. III. "Animal Behavior", 3 (Box 115)
    - Every, Gary. "Muerto and Zopitole", 1 CD
      - Muerto and Zopitole by Gary Every, 2011-ycal-44252-0036; 1 (Box 123)
    - Gross, Hugh. "After The Wizard", 3 (Box 115)
    - Jacob, John. "The Cabin" (Box 115)
    - Jacob, John. "Palaver", 6 (Box 115)
    - Kelley, Collin. Poems and biography, 1 CD
      - Collin Kelley Poems + Bio Chiron Review, 2011-ycal-44252-0037; 1 (Box 123)
    - Kempher, Ruth Moon, editor. "At the Gate: Departures and Arrivals", 4 (Box 115)
    - Kempher, Ruth Moon. "The Chronicles of Madam X" (Box 115)
    - Kempher, Ruth Moon. "Contrarywise: An Anthology", 5 (Box 115)
    - Kempher, Ruth Moon. "Patty Lou Goes to Rutabaga Rose's Family Reunion" (Box 115)
    - Kempher, Ruth Moon. "Patty Lou Meets Rutabaga Rose" (Box 115)
    - Kempher, Ruth Moon. "Sister Hilda" (Box 115)
    - Laws, Kyle, editor. "From the Garret on Grand: On Miss Lonelyhearts and the Virgin of Guadalupe", 2 (Box 115)
    - Long, Virginia Love. "Stones of Silence" (Box 116)
    - Long, Virginia Love. Unidentified (Box 116)
    - Lowe, Fred. Unidentified, 1 CD
      - FRED LOWE, 2011-ycal-44252-0006; 1 (Box 123)
    - Nelson, Rodney. "Mere Telling" (Box 116)
    - Oakes, Philip Byron. "Rain and Bread" (Box 116)
    - Plumell, Kyle. "Stringer", 1 CD
      - Kyle Plumell Stringer ph., 2011-ycal-44252-0030; 1 (Box 123)
    - Slick, Johnny. "Filthomatic" (Box 116)
    - Smith, Wintrhop. "Skin Test", 2 (Box 116)
    - Snyder, Clifton. "Aspens in the Wind", 2 (Box 116)
    - Snyder, Clifton. "Aspens in the Wind", 1 CD
      - Aspens in the Wind Clifton Snider c. 2009, 2011-ycal-44252-0010; 1 (Box 123)
    - Snyder, Clifton. "Winter", 1 CD
      - Winter Snider, 2011-ycal-44252-0011; 1 (Box 123)
    - Stamps, Dana. "Back & Scratch Papyrus" (poems), 1 CD
      - POEMS: Back & Scratch Papyrus Dana Stamps, II. (951) 452-3116, 2011-ycal-44252-0021; 1 (Box 123)
    - Stern, Lee. Unidentified, 2 CDs
      - Lee Stern, 2011-ycal-44252-0039; 1 (Box 123)
      - Lee Stern, 2011-ycal-44252-0038; 1 (Box 123)
    - Steward, D.E., "Torque" (Box 116)
    - Stinger, Ryan and Ken Shedd. "Mental Landscape/ Markings" (Box 116)
    - Wasserman, Martin. "Dripping Blood" (Box 116)
    - Wasserman, Martin. "Forty-Five Hereclitean Poems in Response to Martin Buber" (Box 116)
    - Wasserman, Martin. "The Gunfighter Elegies", 2 (Box 116)
    - Wasserman, Martin. "The Irresistible Hudson: A Haiku Tribute Based on Yiddish Poetry" (Box 116)
    - Watson, Maurice. "Truth V" (Box 116)
    - Wilensky, Ben. Unidentified (Box 116)
    - Wilgus, Neal. "The Leakoids", 3 (Box 116)
    - Winter, Don. "Ad: No way Out But In", 1 CD
      - Ad-- No Way Out But In DON WINTER, 2011-ycal-44252-0034; 1 (Box 123)
    - Unidentified, 31 3.5 inch computer disks
      - pers, 2011-ycal-44252-0042; 1 (Box 125)
      - Personal Mr. Michael Hathaway 702 N Prairie St Saint John, KS 67576, 2011-ycal-44252-0096; 1 (Box 125)
      - Pebo poem League of Lakering poets 5/8/03 translating, 2011-ycal-44252-0075; 1 (Box 125)
      - Ed Ochester interview 10/04 Chiron back covers? Ries on Winter/ Hoet on Lockie RT7 Mother old disk, 2011-ycal-44252-0072; 1 (Box 125)
      - Susan Terris 11 Jordan Avenue San Francisco, CA 94118 Empty The poem I Am Afraid To Write Chickens Have No Myths Take Out/Eat In Photo Op/ Lady W. the Tiger Entitled: The Emperor of Ice Cream Putting Your Money Where Your Mouth Is, 2011-ycal-44252-0103; 1 (Box 125)
      - Aspens/Snider, 2011-ycal-44252-0101; 1 (Box 125)
      - The Calvin 03/09/09, 2011-ycal-44252-0100; 1 (Box 125)
      - Cat Chart.rtf Cat List Cat chores Cosmic cover AMB labels IRS Letter tmplt Mama Jane Med list new poems Resume 11/19/07 wedding Rev Mags photo., 2011-ycal-44252-0067; 1 (Box 125)
      - Terry Mack: 30 Seconds Sara Woodbury: Walton: Truth IV Phillip Oakes:, 2011-ycal-44252-0068; 1 (Box 125)
      - Huntsinger 2/1/03 Watson: New Beg. 3/23/03 Watson: Rick's Place 3/26/03 Tener: Door to Summer 3/24/03 Watson: Miscellanea 4/19/03, 2011-ycal-44252-0069; 1 (Box 125)
      - Kraft: Yankee 10/22/99 Hughes: E'port 7/16/00 Hilton: Women/War 10/10/01, 2011-ycal-44252-0070; 1 (Box 125)
      - 2006 Juanita Brown: Elegies for New Millineum Alan Catlin: thou shalt not kill Virginia: stones or silence, 2011-ycal-44252-0088; 1 (Box 125)
      - Hospital Poems Blue Butterfly, 2011-ycal-44252-0087; 1 (Box 125)
      - Empty Dan Albergotti - 2 poems 1. At the Public Urinal 2. The Story of Harold and Anna Microsoft Word for Mac, 2011-ycal-44252-0104; 1 (Box 125)
      - David Beard, Voices Robert Tener, Let the Darkness Come, 2011-ycal-44252-0055; 1 (Box 125)
      - April intd by Ries 03/06/07, 2011-ycal-44252-0076; 1 (Box 125)
      - SUSAN DELN CLUB spiritual science essays RT7 Mother, 7 years + Revised Maggie's photo The Gut essay aug 2007 01/29/09 e-mail to 1/19/09, 2011-ycal-44252-0102; 1 (Box 125)
      - Kowit - self-deception 7/12/04, 2011-ycal-44252-0054; 1 (Box 125)
      - wilgnsi The Leakoids Mensalingly Winthop Smith; Skim Check 2006-7, 2011-ycal-44252-0053; 1 (Box 125)
      - poems RTF Gaugnier + Shehan, 2011-ycal-44252-0050; 1 (Box 125)
      - Lyons: Freuds Interprelations 7/8/00 Riyeff: Everyday 12/4/00 Inman: Resonances of Begetting 1/28/01, 2011-ycal-44252-0047; 1 (Box 125)
      - Kyle Laws: Garret on Grant 12/15/07, 2011-ycal-44252-0045; 1 (Box 125)
      - animal poo final version Julie 03/28/07 1st draft poems + stones, 2011-ycal-44252-0043; 1 (Box 125)
      - Beard! Interior Prisons Wilgus; Rhyme; Dan... 07/21/04 01/31/05, 2011-ycal-44252-0064; 1 (Box 125)
      - JilliBuege 3/4/07 Song of Love/Praise J. Brown 3/4/07 New Zealand Wilgers 4/14/07 Time to Rhyme - Wasserman 5/18/07, 2011-ycal-44252-0063; 1 (Box 125)
      - Pearn: Postcard from Athens, 2011-ycal-44252-0062; 1 (Box 125)
      - Juanita Brown; Flowers: 01/19/02 Rick Watson: Truth 2 03/17/02 3 03/30/02 JB: Bone to Bone 05/18/02, 2011-ycal-44252-0061; 1 (Box 125)
      - 6/1/08 Buege: Imitations Truth V 6/18/08, 2011-ycal-44252-0060; 1 (Box 125)
      - Catlin Swanberg: Red Lacquer 1/28/01 Watson: Eden Torrence: Flexing cactus 4/8/01, 2011-ycal-44252-0059; 1 (Box 125)
      - Jonny Slick - Filthormatic 2009, 2011-ycal-44252-0058; 1 (Box 125)
      - Voices from the Earth 11/10/01 Lord Byron - Long 9/29/02, 2011-ycal-44252-0056; 1 (Box 125)
  - Poetry events and music performances
    Boxes 121-123 (digital and audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Townsend, Cheryl. "Under Moons" #9, tracks 4 + 5, undated; 1; 00:11:24 (Box 121, Item barcode 39002099363468)
    - "Kyle Laws Radio Show" #3, 2004 March 9; 1; 00:09:23 (Box 121, Item barcode 39002099363450)
    - "Michael McIrvin AB Radio Show" #7, undated; 1; 00:08:00; The program is distorted at times. (Box 121, Item barcode 39002099363443)
    - "Tony Moffeit Radio Show" #13, 2004 February 23; 1; 00:17:50; The program is distorted at times. (Box 121, Item barcode 39002099363435)
    - "David Chorlton #2", 2004 August 7; YCALMSS836_0024; 1; 00:58:03 (Box 121, Item barcode 39002102317378)
    - "Poetry Rendezvous #1", 2004; YCALMSS836_0025; 1; 01:03:04 (Box 121, Item barcode 39002102317386)
    - "Sat. 08/08/04 PR", 2004 August 8; YCALMSS836_0026; 1; 00:56:27 (Box 121, Item barcode 39002102317394)
    - "WOFF Annual Talent Show: Women Over Fifty and their Friends", 2004 October 2; 1 VHS videocassette (Box 122)
    - "Big Ass Party at the Eagle Tavern a Benefit for Lyon-Martin Women's Health Services", 2006 April 13; 1 DVD
      - Big Ass Party at the Eagle Tavern A Benefit for Lyon-Martin Women's Health Services Filmed by: LINDA ZEISER Poet: MC/Montclair Eagle Tavern San Francisco, CA April 13, 2006 Featuring Gwen "Sugar Mama" Avery, J.D. Taylor, Caren Armstrong, Leslie Hassberg, Sabrina Model, Litz "Opera Lady" Plummer, Connie J. Schartz and WILDSANG, 2011-ycal-44252-0001; 1 (Box 123)
    - Mittel, Gabe and McAnulla, Steve. "A Brave Attempt to Separate You From Your Money" (demo), 1 CD
      - A brave attempt to seperate you from your money (Demo) Words by Gabe Mittel Music by Steve McAnulla, 2011-ycal-44252-0015; 1 (Box 123)
    - "Poetry Reading...Linda Sheen Connie Edwards", 2006; 1 CD
      - Poetry Read '06 Linda + Shon Connie Edwards, 2011-ycal-44252-0014; 1 (Box 123)
    - Poetry Rendezvous photographs, 2008 February-July; 1 CD
      - PICS TAKEN FROM 2/08-7/08 Poetry Rendezvous June 2008 Gt Bend KS., 2011-ycal-44252-0107; 1 (Box 123)
    - Unidentified, 7 (Box 117)
  - Other Papers
    - Administrative files, 5 CDs
      - [no label information], 2011-ycal-44252-0023; 1 (Box 123)
      - Mailing list 05/08/09, 2011-ycal-44252-0024; 1 (Box 123)
      - [no label information], 2011-ycal-44252-0025; 1 (Box 123)
      - 1st transfer CD, 2011-ycal-44252-0026; 1 (Box 123)
      - [no label information], 2011-ycal-44252-0027; 1 (Box 123)
    - Photographs, 4 (Box 117)
    - Drawings (Box 117)
    - Unidentified, 2 (Box 117)
    - Unidentified, 1 CD
      - Stringer, 2011-ycal-44252-0031; 1 (Box 123)
    - Unidentified, 15 CDs
      - 9 POETS ALIVE THE RADIO SHOW Jefferey Beam Kyle Laws Fred Lowe Ruth Moon Kempher Michael McIrvin Cheryl Townsend Maggie Jaffe Spiel Tony Moffeit, 2011-ycal-44252-0002; 1 (Box 124)
      - KUNM aircheck 17 Nov 05 Mark Weber's Thursday jazz show, 2011-ycal-44252-0009; 1 (Box 124)
      - KUNM 27 May 10 aircheck Mark Weber Thursday jazz show, 2011-ycal-44252-0007; 1 (Box 124)
      - ZeRX ZERX RECORDS 074 ALBUZERXQUE vol. 29 (c) 2007, 2011-ycal-44252-0106; 1 (Box 124)
      - KUNM 28 jan 10 aircheck Mark Weber Thursday jazz show, 2011-ycal-44252-0013; 1 (Box 124)
      - Fina Sauf, 2011-ycal-44252-0033; 1 (Box 124)
      - [no label information], 2011-ycal-44252-0019; 1 (Box 124)
      - LA LUZ CURRICULUM 2ND YEAR, 2011-ycal-44252-0040; 1 (Box 124)
      - LA LUZ YEAR 4 RTF FORMAT, 2011-ycal-44252-0035; 1 (Box 124)
      - Maggie Jaffe Alpha Beat broadside 2 poems 1 min 20 sec, 2011-ycal-44252-0003; 1 (Box 124)
      - Radio Discs Combined intros Kempher Townsend Jaffe #'s 5, 8, 10 with pauses between, 2011-ycal-44252-0008; 1 (Box 124)
      - Radio Intro to Show Disc #1 2 min 33 sec., 2011-ycal-44252-0004; 1 (Box 124)
      - Ryan - new, 2011-ycal-44252-0017; 1 (Box 124)
      - Spiel A.B. Radio Show 8 min. 55 sec., 2011-ycal-44252-0005; 1 (Box 124)
      - 30 sept 10 aircheck KUNM Mark Weber Thursday jazz show, 2011-ycal-44252-0012; 1 (Box 124)
    - Unidentified, 1 mini-CD
      - Rosewater, 2011-ycal-44252-0041; 1 (Box 124)
    - Unidentified, 12 3.5 inch disks
      - Editorial, 2011-ycal-44252-0094; 1 (Box 125)
      - Poetry - New Editions 07/17/08, 2011-ycal-44252-0098; 1 (Box 125)
      - Prose 6/10/08, 2011-ycal-44252-0097; 1 (Box 125)
      - Poems 6/10/08 Master File 04/04/09, 2011-ycal-44252-0099; 1 (Box 125)
      - 6/18/02 08/02 2002 Ledgers, 2011-ycal-44252-0052; 1 (Box 125)
      - need pc disk ledger mail lists Spider wo Kostelanets, 2011-ycal-44252-0074; 1 (Box 125)
      - Mailing List, 2011-ycal-44252-0095; 1 (Box 125)
      - Library backup 3/31/08 Jill, 2011-ycal-44252-0105; 1 (Box 125)
      - 2/17/2007, 2011-ycal-44252-0051; 1 (Box 125)
      - Lyons: Freud, 2nd ed. 10/17/02, 2011-ycal-44252-0049; 1 (Box 125)
      - [no label information], 2011-ycal-44252-0073; 1 (Box 125)
      - Critter File 05/06/06, 2011-ycal-44252-0071; 1 (Box 125)
- Other Acquisitions, 2003-2006, undated; 2.42; (3 boxes)
  Box 128 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Other Papers
    - Manuscripts removed from books, 35 (Box 126)
    - Manuscripts removed from books, 12 (Box 127)
    - Unidentified, 9 (Box 127)
    - Unidentified, 12 CDs, 1 audiocassette (Box 128)
      - Beer Drinking Hour #20 / from Dan and Margaret Crocker (MO), 2002 March 15; 1; 01:01:26; The program is distorted at times. (Box 128, Item barcode 39002099363427)
- January 2016 Acquisition, circa 1900-2015; 19.01; (20 boxes) + 1 record album storage
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Purchased from Chiron, Inc., on the Danford N. Barney, Jr. Fund, 2016.
  This addition to the archive consists of correspondence, writings, journals, printed material, records, audiovisual materials, electronic media, and other papers relating to Michael Hathaway and Chiron Review.
  - Poetry Rendezvous - 25th Anniversary, 2013 (Box 129)
  - Chiron Review - correspondence, 2013-04-2013-12 (Box 129)
  - The Art of Survival Anthology - galley proofs, 2013 (Box 129)
  - Mailing lists and ledgers, 2005-2011 (Box 129)
  - Prairie Connection, newspaper, 2013-2014 (Box 129)
    - "Rochelle Lynn Holt", 1 (Box 149)
  - The Anya Files, 2013; 1 (Box 149)
  - Jataka Tales, 2012-2013; (3 folders) (Box 130)
  - Metamorphosis - Anya F. Graber, circa 2013; (4 folders) (Box 130)
  - Adult literacy, circa 1970s-1992; (3 folders) (Box 130)
  - "Dachau and Hitler's Summer home destroyed", photographs by Wesley Mays, undated; 1 (Box 149)
  - "Chiron Review job archive" and "Blue Motel," by Ruth Moon Kemper, 2014; 1 (Box 149)
  - Michael Hathaway, datebook, 2011-2015 (Box 130)
  - Michael Hathaway, journal, circa 2013 (Box 130)
  - Michael Hathaway - "Poetry submissions", journal, 2006-2013 (Box 130)
  - Michael Hathaway, journal, 2006-2010 (Box 130)
  - Michael Hathaway, journal, 2006 (Box 130)
  - Poetry submissions, 2015 (Box 130)
    - Chiron Review - correspondence and files, 2010-2015; 2 (Box 149)
  - Correspondence, 2006; (3 folders) (Box 130)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 131)
  - Postcards and postcard book, undated (Box 131)
  - Book plates, postcards and holiday cards, undated (Box 131)
  - Large format postcards and exhibit catalog (Wichita Art Museum), circa 1966 (Box 131)
  - Cynthia Hoff, masters thesis, Fort Hays State University, 1986 (Box 131)
  - "Montana Morning," poem on hand-made floral paper, by Elockie, undated (Box 131)
  - "The Hundred Year Oak," poem on hand-made floral paper, by Elockie, undated (Box 131)
  - Mississippi Delta Tennessee Williams festival, 2013 (Box 131)
  - Steven Sassmann, poetry, 2013 (Box 131)
  - "I Love My Poem," by Tori Fox (elementary school student), circa 2010 (Box 131)
  - Simon & Garfunkel, 1 (Box 149)
  - Newspapers, 2011-2013; (4 folders) (Box 131)
    Contains copies of the Prairie Connection and Rural Messenger.
  - University of Pittsburgh Press, Spring and Summer, 2013 (Box 132)
  - Chiron Review, correspondence, 2011-2013; (2 folders) (Box 132)
  - Chiron Review, correspondence, 2012 (Box 132)
  - University of Pittsburgh Press, Spring and Summer, 2012 (Box 132)
  - Flying Fish and miscellaneous copies, circa 2011 (Box 132)
  - "Aura... For Chizuko," with poetry notes, circa 2000s (Box 132)
  - BURP 4 and BURP 6, circa 2011 (Box 132)
    Contains photocopy of letter, and envelope.
  - Timothy Leo Berens, masters thesis, Fort Hays State University, 1986 (Box 132)
  - Email correspondence, clippings and various material, 1999-2012; (11 folders) (Box 133)
  - "Gabe and Shon," correspondence, circa 2010 (Box 133)
  - Prairie Connection, newspaper, 2013 (Box 133)
  - "Six Voices," corrected typescript, 2014 (Box 133)
  - "Six Voices," empty envelopes with notes, undated (Box 133)
  - "Six Voices," by Hal J. Daniel III, proof, circa 2014 (Box 133)
  - Chiron Review correspondence and other material, circa 2013 (Box 133)
  - "Chiron Review #96 - Sticklor - Misc. Poetry, Autumn", 2011; (2 folders) (Box 134)
  - "Chiron Review #96 - Prose & Features - Sticklor, Autumn", 2011; (2 folders) (Box 134)
  - "Prose - Chiron Review: Orig. Typescripts Issue #95, Summer #2 - Prod.", 2011; (2 folders) (Box 134)
  - "Chiron Review Orig. Typescripts Issue #95, Summer. #1 Poetry", 2011; (2 folders) (Box 134)
  - Correspondence, 2011-04-05-2011-11-05; (2 folders) (Box 134)
  - "Alb Peace King Y Queen of the Gods," by Peace King Al I - drafts, correspondence and proofs, circa 2011 (Box 135)
  - Jeffrey C. Alfier - corresondence, drafts and proofs, circa 2011 (Box 135)
  - Tobi Cogswell - correspondence, drafts and proofs, circa 2011 (Box 135)
    Contains material regarding "Surface Effects in Winter Wind."
  - John Jacob - correspondence, circa 2011 (Box 135)
    Contains material regarding "Palaver."
  - Terry Wright - correspondence and drafts, circa 2011 (Box 135)
    Contains material related to "Graphs."
  - Jeffrey C. Alfier - correspondence, drafts and proofs, circa 2011 (Box 135)
    Contains material regarding "The Torch Singer."
  - Margaret Nelms - correspondence, circa 2011 (Box 135)